Kelly, Edward J. Papers 5867
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- In the Matter of: United Air Lines vs. William Charles Hunt + Association Ex. H-6 (Folder 4 of 5), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- 69-6 Hunt (Folder 6 of 6), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- VAL- ALPA Activity 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Decision in Grievance of William C Brashear Board No. 69-7 Williamson 69-13, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- 1952-1953 Schaumleffel UAL Disciplinary Action, 1953-1964 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- The First Annual Air Safety Conference, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- UAL MEC By-Laws and Rules of Procedure (Folder 1 of 2), 1958 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- UAL MEC By-Laws and Rules of Procedure (Folder 2 of 2), 1958 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Agreement Between United Air Lines Transport Corporation and the United Air Line Pilots in the Service of the United Air Lines Transport Corporation yrs.: 1940, 1942, 1953, 1940-1953 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Agreement between. United Air Lines, Inc. and the Air Line Pilots in the Service of the United Air Lines, Inc. yrs.: 1955, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Agreement between. United Air Lines, Inc. and the Air Line Pilots in the Service of the United Air Lines, Inc yrs:1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Kulweic on Motion 74-11, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Nemeir 73-17, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Geddes/ Mec 74-50, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Roszel Co 34 75-31, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Wilson Co 33 75-28, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Roszel/ West 76-13, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Wilson/ Co 93 76-4, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- O'Keefe 76-3, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Von Gaillen/ Peterson Rennie 74-6, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Malloy/ Cosgrove, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- West/ MEC 73-6, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Geddes/ MEC 74-23, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Long/ Co 33 73-21, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- S. Francis SFO Exec Sess Robertson, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Feneley 74-2, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Traynor/ renisan 73-33, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Notice of Hearing- United Airlines Pilots' System Board of Adjustment, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- McIntyre/ CO 12 74-9, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Mahoney/ Kersh 75-36, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Air Line Pilots Association UAL- MEC- 76-5 W, 75-27 W, 75-22 W 75-29 W 73-16, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Roszel/ Von Gaillen 76-7, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- United Airlines Pilots System Board of Adjustment Board No. 75-7 75-24, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Roszel/ Mulleniex 76-6, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Pierce/Wilsman 76-19, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- United Airline Pilot System Board of Adjustment Board No. 75-3 Chester Kulwiec, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Mahoney/ Harrison 75-30, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Roszel/ Nelson et al 75-34, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Consolidated 73-18 22 36, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Higman 75-25, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Godlove 75-26, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- West MEC 72-25, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Funk 74-25+ 74-65, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Stelmach 73-35, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Kuni/Schultz 75-16, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Long/Co 93 74-3, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Air Line Pilots Association UAL- MEC 75.2 75-14,15 W, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Hardie/ Cohagen 74-45, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Traynor/ Kulwiec 75-3, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Adams 75-13, 1967-1975 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Barry 74-43, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Illegal Lines at ORD Wilsman/ CO12 74-48, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- O' Daniel/ Nugent 74-36, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- United Airlines Pilots' System Board of Adjustment No. 74-45, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- United States District Court For The Western District of Washington, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Christensen 75-6, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Von Gaillenn/ Henricks 75-21 W, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Hardie/ Cohagen 74-45, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Noble/ Gallant 74-32, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Bunker/ CO 33 75-30, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Riley 73- 27, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Stanton/ Quitney 73-29, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Mahoney/ Raymond 74- 37, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Mahoney/ Fitzgerald 74-62, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Mahoney Bosse 74-55, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Geddes/ MEC 74-58, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Noble/ CO 12 74-47, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Rensvold/ CO 34 74-38, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Stanton/ Weinstein 74-7, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Don White + Jeff White 74- 4, 75-5, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Stanton/ Hendricks 73-41, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Noble/ CO12 74-20 W, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Guy/ CO 12 74-54, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Mahoney/ Clayton 74-64, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Pierce/ Mussleman 76-2, 1970-1976 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Wilsman et al 74-26, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Geddes/ MEC 73-8 W Long/ Co 93 73-16 W, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Air Line Pilots Association UAL-MEC Bd No. 74-16, 74-22, 74-30 74-41 74-42 74-66 VanKleef 74-52 O'Daniel/Wolfe 74-59, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Lyall 74-51, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Long/ CO 93 74-4, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Readmon 73-15, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Gary 74-8, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Willsman/ CO 12 74-10, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Stanton/ McEachern 74-24, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Stanton/ CO 34 73-43, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- Noble/ Pressgrove 73-38, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 75)
- Stanton/ Potts 73-28, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Traynor/Lang 74-13, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 77)
- Stanton/ Segars 73-50, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 78)
- Wilsman/ CO 12 72-16, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Stanton/ Carlton 72-14, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Wilsman- Traynor 71-32, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Holder 71-30, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Puckett 70-8, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Geddes J.D. 72-19, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Ankins/ Group 71-38 A, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Silliman 70-14, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Seewald FL 71-36, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- West Valmec 72-1, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Vitelli J.A. 72-18, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- 72-8, 72-6, 72-33, 72-35, 71-24, Cornell T.E. 72-15, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- West- Wisda 72-2, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Aronson H. 71-34, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Vass 70-5, 70-18, 71-4 (Murray Warren Council #52), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Bell 70-4, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- D'Amico 69-34, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- M. De Mitchell 71-2, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Atkins Pressgrove (70-1) Pressgrove (70-9), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Martin 70-34 Withdrawn (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Robison 70-30, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- AJ McClain 69-4 F/1, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Sodergren 70-10, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Jim Sexton 71-10, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Beins 69-41, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Lindfors 70-2, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Crouch 70-41, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Warren 71-1, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Lammerding 71-12, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Chunn- Simpson 71-26, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Schultz 71-3, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Markgraf 71-14, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Holst "Hair" 70-31, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Henricks 70-12, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- TE Cornell 70-23, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- De Mitchell- Geddes 71-28, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- McGinnis 71-27, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Le Beau 71-20, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Wilsman Traynor 71-32 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Watkins 71-33, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Heppler 71-35, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Pogue 70-3, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Brannen 69-38 Snyder 70-7 70-15, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Wilsman Williams Girard Peterson, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Allard 71-24, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Notice of Hearing Grievance of: J.M. Sexton, M. Warren J.L. Crouch, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Crouch 71-7, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- J.D. Geddes 71-16, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- OC Kaintz 71-8, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Kaintz/ Fischer 71-17, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Stanton/Hayes 73-34, 1972-1975 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Bunker Mugleston 73-47, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Wilsman/Co12 + Gary 4- 29, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Moore/ JFK 73-12, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- De Mitchell 73-14, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Letter to Robert H. Nichols Regarding Wilsman Case, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Wilsman 74-14, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Bunker Co 33 73-1, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Bunker/ Co33 74-17, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Noble/Bandfield 74-15, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Noble/Ewing 73-32, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Long/ Co 93 73-46, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Hunt+ Draft, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Hunt and Final UAL Dissent, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Tokle (70-11) Ashford (70-13), 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Mugleson 70-29, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Schroeder 70-32, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Akins 7017, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Warren 71-4, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Fink 72-24, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Hill 69-14 Hilleson 68-19, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Wilsman - Glasby 69-16, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Akins 69-43, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Akins/ Wilkins 69-33, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Silliman 69-23, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Wilsman 69-11, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Akins/Pressgrove 69-30, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- G.E. Barnes 70-37 Backus 70-38 David/ Funk 70-39 David/Spann 70-40, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Dalition 70-22, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Kent 71-18, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- De Mitchell for Mennella (71-23) Murphy Policy (7024) Tappe (70-33) Flight Officers- Appearance Standards, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Greer 71-9, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Mount 73-24, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Moore/ Co 52 73-25, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- McMann 73-10, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Noble/Ballack 72-45, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- J.G. Moore (74-5) Stanton/ Co34, Withdrawn 73-49 A.E. Brayham 73-48 Noble/Co 73-44, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Kendall 72-32, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- KE Ellis 6917, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Akins/ Kasper 69-19, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Akins (69-42) Miller 70-6 Snyder (70-20), 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Page 7-28, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Vass 70-5 (Brodigan Nichols), 1969 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- J. M. Kent 71-5, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Tappe 71-3, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- McDonald 71-11, 1963-1971 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Henze 70-27, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Henricks 70-35, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- No. 70-25 In the Matter of A.A. Akins / B.J. Sohn, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Markgrat 73-31, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Traynor/Dixon 74-12, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Cook. D.D> (71-31) Mahoney-Allen (72-28) Russell (73-37), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Taynor NFM 72-38, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Stanton/Fitzgerald 72-36, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- United Airlines Pilots' System Board of Adjustment Grievance of Joseph Lubozynski Board No. 71-22, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Before the United Air Lines Pilots' System Board of Adjustment: In the Matter of United Air Lines, Inc. and Air Line Pilots Association, International, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Reply Brief on Behalf of Captain Joseph Lubozynski and the Air Line Pilots Association (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Letters to Mark Kahn, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Air Line Pilots Association and United Air Lines, Inc. Grievance of Joseph Lubozynski ALPA Grievance No. CHI- 281-70, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Board No. 71-22 Co x 4- Co x 14, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Co x 15- Co x 20 Ax 1 to Ax 14 Board No. 71-22 ( Lubozynski), 1970 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Lubozynski Board No. 71-22, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Raney A.E. 72-4, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Co x 1 72 Flight Manual Handbook, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Co x 2 to Co x 20 Alpha x 10, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Aircraft Accident Report United Air Lines, Inc. Boeing 727, N7020U Stapleton, International Airport, Denver, Colorado, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Co x 22 to Co x 32 + National Transportation Safety Board Bureau of Aviation Safety, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Board No.73- 39
- AX 1 to Z 26 727 Flight Manual Reference + Review, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- In the Matter of Grievance of A.E. Raney Board No. 72-4, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Aircraft Accident Report Northwest Airlines Inc. + Letters to Benjamin Aaron + Richard F. Watt, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Grievance of John E. (Jeff) White ALPA No. 750U-11-5 Boar No. 75-4 Donald M. Wight J.R., ALPA No. U-11-6, Board No. 75-5, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- In the Matter of Grievance of A.E. Raney Board No. 72-4, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Before the United Lines Pilots' System board of Adjustment, In the Matter of United Air Lines, Inc. and Air Line Pilots Association, International, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Before the United Lines Pilots' System board of Adjustment, In the Matter of United Air Lines, Inc. and Air Line Pilots Association, International, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Air Line Pilots Association and United Air Lines, Inc. Grievance of A.E. Raney ALPA Grievance No. 194-71, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Air Line Pilots Association and United Air Lines, Inc. Grievance of A.E. Raney ALPA Grievance No. 194-71, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Before the United Lines Pilots' System board of Adjustment, In the Matter of Grievance of A.E. Raney Board No. 72-4, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Raney A.E. 72-4, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Correspondence 1973-1974 (Folder 1 of 5), 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Correspondence 1973-1974 (Folder 2 of 5) Law Office Cotton, Watt, Jones, King & Bowlus, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Correspondence 1973-1974 Law Offices, Cotton, Watt, Jones, King + Bowlus and United Airline Pilots System Board of Adjustment (Folder 3 of 5), 1975- 1976 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Correspondence 1973-1974 United Airlines Pilots System Board of Adjustment (Folder 4 of 5), 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Correspondence 1973-1974 United Airlines Pilots System Board of Adjustment (Folder 5 of 5) (Box 12, Folder 17)
- New Submissions 1974 Air Line Pilots Association UAL- MEC (Folder 1 of 5), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- New Submissions 1974 Air Line Pilots Association UAL-MEC (Folder 2 of 5) (Box 12, Folder 19)
- New Submissions 1974 Air Line Pilots Association UAL-MEC (Folder 3 of 5) (Box 12, Folder 20)
- New Submissions 1974 Air Line Pilots Association UAL-MEC (Folder 4 of 5) (Box 12, Folder 21)
- New Submissions 1974 Air Line Pilots Association UAL-MEC (Folder 5 of 5) (Box 12, Folder 22)
- UAL Pilots System Board of Adjustment 69-29, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- ALPA No. 72-7 10 and 30, 31, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- ALPA No. 72-39 and 73-4,7,19,25,26, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- United Air Lines Pilot's System Board of Adjustment No. 73-18,22,36, 72-27, 32,39,1,4,12, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- United Air Lines Pilot's System Board of Adjustment No.73,13,14,15,17,23,24,25,28,31,34, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- United Air Lines Pilot's System Board of Adjustment Board No. 73-38,43,46,47 74-50,4,7,8, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- United Air Lines Pilot's System Board of Adjustment Board No. 74-14,17,21,29, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- United Air Lines Pilot's System Board of Adjustment Board No. 74-27,31,32,37,38,45,51,54,55,62, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Grievance of David Landry for Council 12 Board No. 68-13, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Decision in Grievance of William C. Brashar Board No. 69-7, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Decision in the Grievance of Joseph P. David Board No. 69-8, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Uncle No. 69-1, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Betsworth 69-3, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Willsman 69-5, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Wilsman- Co 12 72-3, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Wilsman- Rose 72-11, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Feinberg H. 72-29, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Benn 72-12, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Roddy 72-5, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- West/ MEC 72-7, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Moore JG 72-17, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Shoup 72-9, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Stanton/ Nord 72-34 and N.C. Whittenfeld 73-9Stanton/Nord 72-34 + N.C. Whittenfeld 73-9, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Traynor/ Meyer (72-37) Geddes/ Donovan (73-5), 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Traynor/Soldering (73-11) Snyder/Co.93 (70-16), 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Geddes/ Broom, Meloche, McQuarrie 73-4, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Moss Miller Wilsman Kincaid (68-6) Pike Det Mag.(68-14) Hunt Disch (69-6) Wilsman (69-10), 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Powell (69-9) Willsman (69-13) Landry (69-18) Wilsman/Peterson (69/24) Akins/Gregory (69-25) Wilsman (69-27) Sohn (69-32), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Wilsman-Sanders 72-13, 1964-1974 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Frontier Wet Lease 71-37, 1968-1974 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- COX 22 to COX 32 + National Transportation Safety Board Bureau of Aviation Safety, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Aug. 72 ALPA (Folder 1 of 2), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Aug 72 ALPA Folder 2 of 2), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Before the Pilot's System Board of Adjustment, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Mittenthal, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- United Air Lines Pilot's System Board of Adjustment Grievance of J.X .Traynor et al 72-27+ No. 76-11, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Correspondence-Cotton, Watt, Jones, King+ Bowlus Mayer, Brown+ Platt (Folder 1 of 4), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Correspondence-Cotton, Watt, Jones, King+ Bowlus Mayer, Brown+ Platt (Folder 2 of 4), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Correspondence-Cotton, Watt, Jones, King+ Bowlus Mayer, Brown+ Platt (Folder 3 of 4), 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Correspondence-Cotton, Watt, Jones, King+ Bowlus Mayer, Brown+ Platt (Folder 4 of 4), 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Roszel-Gilbert-Donnegan Buck 75-32 and No 76-1 Sherman, Stunton, Miller, Burns, Brayham, Tabor, West, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Kinery L.A. (Wagner) 76-9, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Dubinsky FC Hair 77-1 (Wagner), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Wilson/Co93 75-23 (Wagner), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Cont. Mahoney /Co5 75-35 (Wagner), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Kinery Dissent Board No. 76-9 + No. 74-4 McIntyre/Council 12, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Piece Chamber 77-12 (Cont.) Kahn, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Grievance of DeMitchell/ Geddes Boar No. 71-28, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Moore/JFK (Kahn) 73-20 DC. 8, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Tandy 74-53 (Kahn), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Notice of Hearing Board No. 73-20,77-11,77-12,74-63 74-63, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Fink (73-3) Ray and Geddes/ MEC (73-8) (Kahn), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Fancher (77-11) Co34 Mahoney/ Schlichter 74-63 (Kahn), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Stripe 69-26, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Stripe Case, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- OZA # 134 General Correspondence (1969) (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Exhibit A to Exhibit F Grievance of Frederick Stripe, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Company Exhibit G to J (Stripe), 1953-1956 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- (Draft) Stripe (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Flight Operations Manual, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Bailey Thos. J 68-8, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Grievance of David Landry for Council 12 Board No. 68-13, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Decision in Grievance of William C. Brashear Board No. 69-7, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Decision in the Grievance Board No. 69-8 of Joseph P. David, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- UNKLE Discharge Alteration of Tickets, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Betsworth 69-3, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Willsman 69-5, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Wilsman- Co12 72-3, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Wilsman-Rose 72-11, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Feinberg H. 72-29, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Benn 72-12, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Roddy 72-5, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- West/ MEC 72-7, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Moore JG 72-17, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Shoup 729, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Stanton/Nord (72-34) + N.C. Whittenfeld (73-4), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Traynor/Meyer (72-37) Geddes/ Donovan (73-5), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Traynor/Soderling 73-11 Snyder/Co.93 70-16, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Geddes/Broom (73-4) Meloche, McQuarrie, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Moss, Miller, Wislman Kincaid (68-6)Pike Det. Mag (68-14)Hunt Disch (69-6) Wilsman (60-10), 1968 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Powell (69-9) Willsman (64-13) Akins/Gregory 69-25 Landry (69-18 Wilsman/Peterson (69-24) Wilsman (69-27) Sohn (69-32), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Wilsman-Sanders72-13, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Frontier Wet Lease 71-37, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Flight Engineers, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- PHA Negotiations 1955 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- System Seniority vs. Dom Seniority, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Agreements Other than U.A.L., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Agreements Other than UAL, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Opening Letter to Company, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- DC-7 Arbitration, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Co. Negotiations Opening Letter, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Negotiations Committee, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Lovett J.H. Eng&; Air Safety, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Bunks in DC 7, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Dexter Iowa Convair Accident, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- C- Band Radar, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Courtney Bennett Transfer, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Senate Bill 2647, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Abby Report on Chart Holders, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Negotiating Committee 1954 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Dehmel, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Dehmal Trainer Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Dehmel Policy, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Dehmel/Grievance, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Letter to UAL MEC Members R.F. Ahrens and Clarence N. Sayen, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Contract Interpretations Company and Pilot, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- 1954 Negotiations (Box 14, Folder 30)
- UAL Opening Letter + Negotiations, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- 1953 Contract Interpretations (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Gen. Corr, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Grievance LGA Information and Corr., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- System Board General, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Jerry Prom Discharge Case, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Air Line Pilots Association-Letter to W.E. Fallon, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Anders/Berghower- Savage Case, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Flight Officers-Temp Assignments Etc., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- MEC Meeting Feb. 8-9, 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Operations Specifications U.S. Flag Carriers, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Merger Cont. + Branif (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Mechanic Relations General, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- ALPA Building, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Mutual AID Plan, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- ALPA Building, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Eng. And Air Safety Committee, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Eng. + Air Safety Action File (To Do), 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- MEC Correspond. General, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Flight Times Limitations, 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Contract Negotiations, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Interchange Agreement Corr. And Drafts Etc., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- MEC, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Committee File, 1953-1955 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- PDX and SLC Domiciles, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Flight Time Delay Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Ransom Case, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- CIRVIS, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Work Drafts Contract Etc., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Follow UP, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- CHI LGA Pilot Move Run Holders, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- UAL MEC Officers Amendment to Agreement Between United Air Lines, Inc. and the Air Line Pilots in the Service of United Air Lines Inc., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Portman Eng.&; Air Safety, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Uniform Committee, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- ALPA Legal Brubaker, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Wagner Questionnaire, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Krolft-Sayne, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- DEN Hotel and Room Correspondence, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- DC-7 Dead Heading Lloyd Treeve Appointment + System Board, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Telegrams Sent, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Telegrams Received, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Baschen Grievance, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 14)